thecontaminated.com 2013-09-26

# Privacy Policy | TheContaminated - Cool Pictures, Weird Pictures, Funny Pictures

thecontaminated.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

Third Party Advertising  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Personal Information  
We do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. Thecontaminated.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.

Amazing Stories

#### [9 Features that Boost Your Home Value](http://thecontaminated.com/9-features-that-boost-your-home-value/ "9 Features that Boost Your Home Value")

Updated Kitchen A kitchen can be a real selling point in a house. It is one of the main rooms that people look at and if it is out of date, they will worry about the expense of making it look good whe...

#### [The Biggest Poker Wins Ever](http://thecontaminated.com/the-biggest-poker-wins-ever/ "The Biggest Poker Wins Ever")

When playing poker it can always be great to dream about making a massive win. It can really inspire you to keep playing if you find out more about people who win big. Some people will be professional...

Cool Stuff

#### [5 Bedding Options for Kids Rooms](http://thecontaminated.com/5-bedding-options-for-kids-rooms/ "5 Bedding Options for Kids Rooms")

If you have a child, then you may just think they will need a regular bed, once they have outgrown their cot. However, there are a whole range of options out there and it is worth considering them all...

#### [Keeping Your Drink Looking and Tasting Cool!](http://thecontaminated.com/keeping-your-drink-looking-and-tasting-cool/ "Keeping Your Drink Looking and Tasting Cool!")

Everyone knows that having a cool drink is a must. Drinking out of a bottle or can in the summer can be extremely unpleasant if the drink is not cool and if it is kept out in the hot sun or in a warm ...

#### [How Women Bands Looked Like a Few Decades Ago](http://thecontaminated.com/how-women-bands-looked-like-a-few-decades-ago/ "How Women Bands Looked Like a Few Decades Ago")

It seems that women in past have been as same active in the world of music and stage arts as they are today. Despite the fact we think that human society was way more conservative about forty or fifty...

Technology

#### [Best Graphing Calculators for iPhone/iPad/iOS](http://thecontaminated.com/best-graphing-calculators-for-iphoneipadios/ "Best Graphing Calculators for iPhone/iPad/iOS")

There are many calculators apps for iPhones and considering we have been using the calculators on our phones long before we had iPhones (in fact we often used them on our digital watches), they are a ...
